<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on aarvik.org</title>
    <link>https://aarvik.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on aarvik.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>bendik@aarvik.org (Bendik Aarvik)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>bendik@aarvik.org (Bendik Aarvik)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:30:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aarvik.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Incident Management with ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://aarvik.org/streamlining-incident-management-with-chatgpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>bendik@aarvik.org (Bendik Aarvik)</author>
      <guid>https://aarvik.org/streamlining-incident-management-with-chatgpt/</guid>
      <description>Sentinel and ChatGPT My latest obsession, like many others, has been ChatGPT. Everything from making detailed backstories to fictional characters to brainstorming how to finish a sentence. Here my intentions are to go through some of my findings regarding using ChatGPT to help me with my work. Specifically incident investigation in Sentinel.
Using ChatGPT for Incident Triage in Azure Sentinel One of the key tasks in incident management is triaging incidents to determine their severity, priority, and next steps for resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of MFA</title>
      <link>https://aarvik.org/the-evolution-of-mfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>bendik@aarvik.org (Bendik Aarvik)</author>
      <guid>https://aarvik.org/the-evolution-of-mfa/</guid>
      <description>The Evolution of MFA: From Single Passwords to passwordless Authentication In the early days of the internet, it was common for people to use just a single password to secure their accounts. This seemed like a sufficient measure at the time, but as more and more personal and sensitive information started being shared online, the need for better security measures became evident. This is where MFA, or Multi Factor Authentication, comes in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring to stay ahead</title>
      <link>https://aarvik.org/monitoring-to-stay-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 09:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>bendik@aarvik.org (Bendik Aarvik)</author>
      <guid>https://aarvik.org/monitoring-to-stay-ahead/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring to stay ahead of the threat landscape It is often difficult to catch everything that is crawling around your network. It is especially hard to catch what is outside your network. It is also where new vulnerabilities get discovered day by day and hour by hour.
Recently there was a Zero-Day vulnerability in exchange that shook the industry. Thankfully, Microsoft was early out with mitigation steps so people could secure their systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
